Take what's yours.
Reclaim is a thriller film directed by Alan White.
After their newly adopted daughter goes missing in a small town, Steven and Shannon will stop at nothing to uncover
the truth behind her disappearance and the dangerous secret behind the adoption agency they trusted.
Risking their own lives, they will discover just what being a parent
means and how far they will go to get their child back.
Benjamin, played by John Cusack.
Steven, played by Ryan Phillippe.
Shannon, played by Rachelle Lefevre.
Reigert, played by Jacki Weaver.
Superintendent, played by Luis Guzmán.
Nina, played by Briana Roy.
Reclaim is a 2014 American action thriller film directed
by Alan White and starring John Cusack.
The film was released on video on demand, with a simultaneous limited
theatrical release in the United States, on September 19, 2014.
Ryan Phillippe and Rachelle Lefevre play an American couple who travel to Puerto Rico
to adopt an orphan (Briana Roy), and become entangled in a deadly scam.
The film explores themes of daughter, adoption, travel, couple, cheat.
The tone is intense.